A Guide to the Christian de Duve papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 2009:084 FA934
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Müller, Lindmark and Mack, Trichomonas Vaginalis – Metabolism and the Mode of Action of Anti-Trichomonad Nitroimidazole, 1978 (Box 32)
- Mack and Müller, End Products of Carbohydrate Metabolism in T. vaginalis, 1980 (Box 32)
- Energy Metabolism of G. lamblia, Lindmark, D. G, 1979 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Lysosomotropic Chemotherapy, 1977 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Publications, 1979-1980 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Basic Research in Developing and Other Countries. In "Health Policies in Developing Countries". page 53-56, 1980 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Autobiographical Note in McGraw Hill "Modern Scientists and Engineers, Volume I", 1980 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, "The Role of Mitochondria…" in Cell Compartmentation and Metabolic Channeling, 1980 (Box 32)
- de Duve, Christian, Cellular Seneschence Forum Medici, Interdisciplinary Gerontology, Platt, D., ed. (Nyon Ch. 1260), 1979 March (Box 32)
- Müller, The Hydrogenosome, 1979 (Box 32)
- Müller, Mode of Action of Metronidazole on Anaerobic Microorganisms, 1979 (Box 32)
- Post-Congress Review, Lloyd and Müller, Vth International Congress Proto., 1974-1979 (Box 32)
- National Institute of Health (NIH), Documents, 1962-1966 (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971 (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971 (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Figures, Reprints (Box 32)
- Correspondence with Editors, Publishers (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques and Information (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970 (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques and Information (Box 32)
- Correspondence with Editors, Publishers (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Figures, Reprints (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969 (Box 32)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques and Information (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Talks, Manuscripts, Reprints (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 32)
- Domagk, G. F. (Box 32)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 32)
- Correspondence, 1968 (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 33)
- Association for the Advancement of Aging Research (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Talks, Articles, Manuscripts, etc. (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
- Correspondence, 1967 (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Talks, Articles, Manuscripts, etc. (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Lab Visitors, Recommendations (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1966 (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Articles, Theses, Manuscripts, etc. (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Positions, Recommendations,… (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 33)
- Italy, 1963-1964 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962 (Box 33)
- Correspondence Prior to 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 33)
- Formal Invitations, 1962-1975 (Box 33)
- Rockefeller University (RU), Cellular Pathology, 1971 (Box 33)
- Manuscript CIBA Foundation Symposium on Lysosomes, 1963 (Box 33)
- Grant Applications, Information Exchange Group, 1964-1966 (Box 33)
- Correspondence (Box 33)
- Lists of Names (Box 33)
- Information (Box 33)
- Information Exchange Group 1 (Box 33)
- Institute Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 33)
- Institute Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 33)
- Budget Statements, Fiscal Year 1964 (Box 33)
- Institutional Budget Proposal, 1965-1966 (Box 33)
- Institute Budget Correspondence (Box 33)
- Institute Budget Decision (Box 33)
- Institute Budgets Before 1965-1966 (Box 33)
- Institutional Budget Decision, 1964-1965 (Box 33)
- Institute Budgets Before 1965-1966 (Box 33)
- Institute Budget Proposals, 1964-1965 (Box 33)
- Institute Budgets Before 1964-1965 (Box 33)
- Rockefeller Institute No. 1, Official, 1964-1969 (Box 33)
- Buildings, 1961-1963 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-I, 1979 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-R, 1979 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1979 (Box 33)
- Refusals/General, 1978-1979 (Box 33)
- Rockefeller University, Interoffice, 1979 (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Publications, etc, 1979 (Box 33)
- Christmas Lectures (Box 33)
- Autograph Requests (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Conference and Organizational Files, 1978-1979 (Box 33)
- Cell Biology and Pathology, 1971 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978 (Box 33)
- Correspondence with the President, Rockefeller University, 1978 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-I (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-R (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Publications, etc. (Box 33)
- Rockefeller University, Inter-office Correspondence (Box 33)
- ICP-General Correspondence (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977 (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 33)
- Autograph Requests (Box 33)
- ICP-General Correspondence (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques and Info (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Reprints, Figures (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975 (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques and Information (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Reprints, Figures (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 33)
- ICP-General Correspondence (Box 33)
- Autograph Requests (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975 (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Reprints, Figures (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 34)
- Autograph Requests (Box 34)
- Correspondence with Editors, Publishers (Box 34)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
- ICP-General Correspondence (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques and Information (Box 34)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974 (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Reprints, Figures (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques and Information (Box 34)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 34)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973 (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Reprints, Figures (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques and Information (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 34)
- Correspondence with Editors, Publishers (Box 34)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Reprints, Figures (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Positions (Box 34)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Visitors to the Lab (Box 34)
- Correspondence with Editors, Publishers (Box 34)
- Correspondence on Scientific Techniques, Publications (Box 34)
- Ohkuma, Chudzik, and Poole (Folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 34)
- Submitted, 1985 June 28 (Box 34)
- Shoji's Paper, Statistical Calculations (Box 34)
- Ohkuma, Chudzik, and Poole (Folder 2 of 2), 1985 (Box 34)
- Shoji (Box 34)
- de Duve, Christian, Peroxisomes and Related Particles in Historical Perspective, 1981 (Box 34)
- Lazarow, Properties of the Natural Precursor of Catalase: … (Box 34)
- Gyang, Poole and Trager, Peptidases from Plasmodium falciparum in vitro, 1981-1982 (Box 34)
- Müller, M., Workshop No. 1. Alternate Metabolic Pathways in Protozoan Energy Metabolism. Parasitology, 1981 (Box 34)
- Fong and Poole, "The Effect of Canavanine on Protein Synthesis and Protein Degradation IMR-90 Fibroblasts", 1981-1982 (Box 34)
- McLaughlin, Müller, "A Calcium Regulated Adenosine Triphosphatase…", Submitted to MBP, 1980 October-1981 (Box 34)
- de Duve, Christian, A Short History of Tissue Fractionation (J. Cell Biol.), 1979-1982 (Box 34)
- Yau- Young, Shio, and Fowler, "Growth, Biochemistry and Morphology of Isolated Rabbit Aortic Smooth Muscle Cells…" (Box 34)
- Ohkuma, Poole, Cytoplasmic Vacuolation of Mouse Peritoneal… JCP, 1980 August 5 (Box 34)
- Poole and Ohkuma, The Effect of Weak Bases…: Submitted JCB, 1980 August 5 (Box 34)
- Lindmark, Activation and Uptake of Polynuclear Aromatic Hydrocarbons, etc. (Box 34)
- de Duve, Christian, "Le lysosome: Essai d'une Esquisse…", Archive de Biologie, 1980 December (Box 34)
- de Duve, Christian, Notice sur la vie et l'oeuvre de C.H. Best, Bulletin de l'Académie Royale de Medicine de Belgique, 1978 (Box 34)
- de Duve, Christian, Lysomotropic Agents as Drugs and as Carriers for Drugs, Submitted 1980 October 27, Merck…Symposium (Box 34)
- An Introduction to Cellular Pathology, Christian de Duve, 1977 (Box 34)
- de Duve, Christian, The Price of Wisdom, 1975-1976 (Box 34)
- de Duve, Christian and Fowler, S., "Subcellular Events in Atherosclerosis", Submitted 1979 April 4, Science (Box 34)
- de Duve, Christian, Trouet, Deprez-de Campeneere and Baurain, "Liposomes as Lysomotropic Carriers" (Box 34)
- Reprints (Box 35)
- Poole, Ohkuma and Warburton, "Protein Degradation in Cells in Culture", 1980 (Box 35)
- Poole, "Synthesis and Degradation of Proteins in Relation to Cellular Structure", 1977 (Box 35)
- Poole, Ohkuma and Warburton, "The Accumulation of Weakly Basic Substances in Lysosomes and the Inhibition of Intracellular Protein Degradation", 1977 (Box 35)
- Davidson and Poole, "Fractionation of the Rat Liver Enzymes That Hydrolyze Benzoyl- Arginine-2-Naphthylamide", 1975 (Box 35)
- Poole", The Kinetics of Disappearance of Labeled Leucine from the Free Leucine Pool of Rat Liver and Its Effect on the Apparent Turnover of Catalase and Other Hepatic Proteins", 1971 (Box 35)
- Poole and Wibo, "Protein Degradation in Cultured Cells", 1973 (Box 35)
- Warburton and Poole, "Effect of Medium Composition on Protein Degradation and DNA Synthesis in Rat Embryo Fibroblasts", 1977 (Box 35)
- Poole, Higashi, and de Duve, Christian, "The Synthesis and Turnover of Rat Liver Peroxisomes. III. The Size Distribution of Peroxisomes and the Incorporation of New Catalase", 1970 (Box 35)
- Wibo and Poole, "Protein Degradation in Cultured Cells. II. The Uptake of Cloroquine by Rat Fibroblasts and the Inhibition of Cellular Protein Degradation and Cathepsin B1", 1974 (Box 35)
- Poole, "Diffusion Effects in the Metabolism of Hydrogen Peroxide by Rat Liver Peroxisomes", 1975 (Box 35)
- Sun and Poole, "Fractionation of Rat Fibroblasts in a Zonal Rotor by Means of a Viscosity Barrier", 1975 (Box 35)
- Davidson, Fowler, and Pool, "An Automated Method for the Fluorescamine Reaction Using a Peristaltic Pump", 1975 (Box 35)
- Poole, "Biogenesis and Turnover of Rat Liver Peroxisomes", 1969 (Box 35)
- Advisory Board, Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1976 (Box 35)
- Overseas Advisory Panel, Biochemical Journal, 1975-1978 (Box 35)
- Molecular and Cellular Biochemistry, 1979-1980 (Box 35)
- PNAS Publications, 1982-1984 (Box 35)
- Migone, N., et al. "Multiple Gene Deletions Within the Human Immunoglobulin…." (Box 35)
- Bontemps, Van Den Berghe and Hers, Evidence for a Substrate Cycle Between AMP and Adenosine in Isolated Hepatocyte" (Box 35)
- van Pell, Aline, and Thierry Boon: Protection Against a Non-Immunogenic (Box 35)
- PNAS Publications, 1981 (Box 35)
- Trouet, Masquelier, Baurain and Deprez-de-Campeneere (Box 35)
- Van Schaftingen, E. and H-Gery Hers (Box 35)
- Van Schaftingen, E., Jett, Hue and Hers: Control of Liver Phosphofructokinase by Frustose (Box 35)
- PNAS Publications, 1976-1980 (Box 35)
- Klinkert, LaBadie, O'Brien, Beyer, and Bowers, Dendritic Cells…Control (Box 35)
- Godelaine, Daniele, Henry Beaufay, and Maurice Wibo (Box 35)
- Robbi and Lazarow, 1978 (Box 35)
- Bartholeyns, Jacques, and Pierre Baudhuin (Box 35)
- Beyer, Carl F., and William E. Bowers (Box 35)
- Feliu, Juan E., Louis Hue, and Henri-Géry Hers (Box 35)
- PNAS Publications, 1977-1978 (Box 35)
- Boon, Thierry, O. Kellermann (Box 35)
- Warburton, Michael J., Brian Poole (Box 35)
- Ohkuma, Poole, 1978 (Box 35)
- de Duve, Christian, Selection by Differential Molecular Survival… (Box 35)
- Rachubinski, et al: Cloning of cDNA Coding for Peroxisomal Acyl-Coa Oxidase (Box 35)
- Shoji, Version 2 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology Reviews, 1975-1983 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology, 1980-Present, 1983 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology: Instructions to Authors (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology Reviews, 1977 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology Reviews, 1976 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology Reviews, 1975 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology, Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology, 1971-1983 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology Reviews, 1974 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology Reviews, 1973 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology Reviews, 1972 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology Reviews, 1971 (Box 35)
- Journal of Cell Biology, 1971-1983 (Box 35)
- 1972-1982, 1972-1983 (Box 35)
- Reviews on Submitted Journal Articles, 1973-1978 (Box 36)
- Acta Clinica Belgica (Box 36)
- Analytical Biochemistry (Box 36)
- Archives of Biochemistry Biophysics (Box 36)
- The Biochemical Journal (Box 36)
- Biochemistry (Box 36)
- Cancer Research (Box 36)
- Biochimica et Biophysica Acta (Box 36)
- Experimental Cell Research (Box 36)
- Reviews on Submitted Journal Articles, 1973-1978 (Box 36)
- Molecular and Cellular Biochemistry (Box 36)
- Miscellaneous Journal Article Critiques, 1974 (Box 36)
- Miscellaneous Journal Article Critiques, 1973 (Box 36)
- Refusals to Evaluate Manuscripts, 1978 (Box 36)
- Reviews and Refusals of Evaluations, 1978 (Box 36)
- Journal of Cell Biology, 1968-1971 (Box 36)
- Enzymologia, 1972 (Box 36)
- Preparative Biochemistry, 1970 (Box 36)
- Publication Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 36)
- Chemotherapy II, In Search of a "Magic Bullet", Christian de Duve, 1976 (Box 36)
- Rosebaum and Glick, 1969 (Box 36)
- Techniques of Biochemical and Biophysical Morphology (Box 36)
- Gottschalk-Aronson Paper, 1969 (Box 36)
- McGraw-Hill, Series on The Cell, 1966 (Box 36)
- Publication Refusuals, 1967-1973 (Box 36)
- Biomembranes I (Box 36)
- Nobel Publications, 1974-1975 (Box 36)
- Manuscripts Already Published, 1976 (Box 36)
- Lindmark and Müller, et al, Berrse Papers (Box 36)
- Gaunt and de Duve: Sub-cellular Distribution of D-Amino Acid in Rat (Box 36)
- Müller and Lindmark, Uptake of Metronidazole and its Effect on Viability in Trichomanades (Box 36)
- Lazarow and de Duve: A Fatty acyl-Coa Oxidizing System in Rat Liver Peroxisomes…. (Box 36)
- Manuscripts Already Published, 1976 (Box 36)
- D.D. Despommier and Müller, The Stichosome and its Secretion Granules in...Trichinella Spiralis (Box 36)
- Müller and Lindmark, Uptake of Metronidazole and its Effect…Trichomonades and Entamoeba in Invadens (Box 36)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts Already Published, 1975 (Box 36)
- Beyer and Bowers, Periodate and Concanavalin-A Induce Blast Transformation of Rat Lymphocytes (Box 36)
- Davidson, Fowler and Poole, An Automated Method for the Fluorescamine Reaction Using a Peristoltic Pump (Box 36)
- Davidson and Poole, Fractionation of Rat Liver Enzymes that Hydrolize BANA (Benzoyl-Arginine-2-Naphthylamide) (Box 36)
- Poole, Lysosomes, Permeability of Membranes and Internal Ph (Box 36)
- Müller, Biochemistry of Protozoan Microbodies (Box 36)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts Already Published, (1973)-1975 (Box 36)
- Poole ,The Inhibition of Cellular Protein Degradation in Rat Fibroblasts (Box 36)
- Poole and Christian de Duve, Properties of Lysosomes and Their Possible…., 1973 (Box 36)
- Poole and Wibo, Studies on the Mechanism of Degradation of Cellular Proteins, 1973 (Box 36)
- Lindmark, Müller, and Shio, Hydrogenosomes in T. vaginalis (Box 36)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts Already Published, 1974-1975 (Box 36)
- de Duve, Christian, Exploring Cells with a Centrifuge (Box 36)
- Sun and Poole, Fractionation of Rat Fibroblasts in a Zonal Rotor…. (Box 36)
- Yago and Bowers, Unique Cathepsin D-Type Proteases in Rat…. (Box 36)
- Poole, Diffusion Effects in the Metabolism of Hydrogen… (Box 36)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts Already Published, 1974 (Box 37)
- The Participation of Lysosomes in the Transformation of Smooth Muscle Cells, Christian de Duve (Box 37)
- The Participation of Lysosomes in the Transformation of Smooth Muscle Cells, Christian de Duve (Box 37)
- Takano, et al, Assay, Kinetics, and Lysosomal Vocalization (Box 37)
- Wibo and Poole, Protein Degradation in Cultured Cells. II (Box 37)
- Bowers, Graft-Vs.-Host and Cytotoxic Activity of Rat Thoracic Duct Lymphocytes and Fractionated…. (Box 37)
- A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, 1982-1983 (Box 37)
- A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, 1982-1983 (Box 37)
- A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, 1982-1983 (Box 37)
- A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, 1982-1983 (Box 37)
- Miller, O. L., 1972 (Box 37)
- Beermann, W. (Box 37)
- Wittmann, H. G., 1982 (Box 37)
- Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
- Scientific Symbol Key (Box 37)
- Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
- A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, 1984 (Box 37)
- A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, Illustrations (Box 37)
- Chapter 12, Extras (Box 37)
- Reprint, JCB, Volume Dedicated to Albert Claude, 1971 (Box 38)
- Heuser, John, 1983 (Box 38)
- A Guided Tour of the Living Cell, Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 38)
- Reprints, Before 1950 (Box 38)
- Reprints, 1950-1955 (Box 38)
- Reprints, 1956 (Box 38)
- Reprints, 1957 (Box 38)
- Reprints, 1958 (Box 38)
- Reprints, 1959 (Box 38)
- Reprints, 1960 (Box 38)
- Reprints, 1961 (Box 38)
- Reprints, A-M, 1962 (Box 38)
- Reprints, N-Z, 1962 (Box 38)
- Reprints, A;F, 1963 (Box 38)
- Reprints, G-Z, 1963 (Box 39)
- Reprints, A-D, 1964 (Box 39)
- Reprints, E-L, 1964 (Box 38)
- Reprints, M-Z, 1964 (Box 38)
- Loose Reprints, 1968-1978 (Box 39)
- Reprint, Rosing, Kayalar and Boyer, Probes of Energy Input in ATP Formation by Oxidative Phosphorylation, 1975 (Box 39)
- Miscellaneous, Notes on Bioenergetics, Christian de Duve (Box 39)
- Bioenergetics Course, 1976-1978 (Box 39)
- Reprint, Christian de Duve, Le développement de centrifugeuses à haute vitesse et leurs applications au fractionnement cellulaire, 1980 (Box 39)
- de Duve, Christian, Foreword from "Drug Carriers in Biology and Medicine", 1979 (Box 39)
- In Memoriam, Guy Michel de Visscher, 1981 (Box 39)
- "Notice sur la vie et l'oeuvre de Michel de Visscher, Membre Titulaire", Christan de Duve, 1981 (Box 39)
- Beaufay, Amar-Costesec and Christian de Duve, Topology of Enzymes in Microsomes from Liver, 1981 (Box 39)
- de Duve: Summary- International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology, 1981 (Box 39)
- de Duve, Christian, De biologische revolutie, 1981 (Box 39)
- Loose Manuscript Notes, 1968-1970 (Box 39)
- Rosing and Slater, The Value of (Delta)G(degree) for the Hydrolosis of ATP, 1972 (Box 39)
- Slater, E. C., Harvey Lecture, The Mechanism of Energy Conservation in the Mitochondrial Respiratory Chain, 1970 October 22 (Box 39)
- Bioenergetics Bulletin, Vol. 2, No. 8 and 9, 1970 November-December (Box 39)
- Information Exchange Group No. 1, Oxidative Phosphorylation and Terminal Electron Transport, 1966-1967 (Box 39)
- Information Exchange Group No. 1, Oxidative Phosphorylation and Terminal Electron Transport, 1966-1967 (Box 40)
- Slater and Berden, High-Energy Forms of Cytochrome b, 1972 (Box 40)
- Notes on Slides (Box 40)
- Bioenergetics Bulletin: Vols. 1 and 2, 1969-1970 (Box 40)
- Information Exchange Group No. 1, Oxidative Phosphorylations and Terminal Electron Transport (Box 40)
- Charts and Graphs (Box 40)
- de Duve, Christian, Harvey Lecture, The Separation and Characterization of Subcellular Particles, 1965 (Box 40)
- Bulletin de l' Academie Royale de Medicine de Belgique, Exposé de M. Christian De Duve, 1968 (Box 40)
- Pontificiae Academiae Scientiarum Documenta, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
- Clinician, Vol. 25, No. 268, 1977 (Box 40)
- Les lysosomes: Travaux présentés à Louvain, sous la présidence du profeseur Christian de Duve, dans le cadre des journées médicales de Bruxelles, 1966 (Box 40)
- Notes on Manuscripts (Box 40)
- Manuscript, Chapters 1-5 (Box 40)
- Manuscript, Chapter 4-5 (Box 40)
- Article, La recherché de pointe en Belgique, l' Institut International de Pathologie Cellulaire et Moléculaire (Box 40)
- Qu'apporte la biologie moderne à la medicine? Le paradoxe de la revolution biologique, 1977-1978 (Box 40)
- JCB, Schneider, Christian de Duve, Trouet, Fate of Plasma Membrane During Endocytosis, III. Evidence for Incomplete Breakdown of Immunoglobulins in Lysosomes of Cultured Fibroblasts (Box 40)
- Manuscript, Le concept de lysosome et ses applications: par M. Christian de Duve (Box 40)
- Manuscript, Chemotherapy with Lysosomotropic Carriers (Box 40)
- Manuscript, Bioenergetics (Box 40)
- Manuscript, Chapter 7, The Cytochromes (Box 40)
- Student Essays, Bioenergetics, 1968-1969 (Box 40)
- Bioenergetics Correspondence, 1968 (Box 40)
- Bioenergetics Problems (Box 40)
- Bioenergetics Notes (Box 40)
- Tables and Figures (Box 40)
- de Duve, Christian, and Baudhuin, Peroxisomes (Microbodies and Related Particles), 1966 (Box 41)
- Coffey and Christian de Duve: Digestive Activity of Lysosomes. I, 1968 (Box 41)
- Aronson and Christian de Duve, Digestive Activity of Lysosomes. II, 1968 (Box 41)
- Poole, Leighton and Christian de Duve, The Synthesis and Turnover of Rat Liver Peroxisomes. II, 1969 (Box 41)
- Baggiolini, Hirsch and Christian de Duve, Resolution of Granules from Rabbit…, 1969 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Summation of the Session on "Intracellular Localization", 1969 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Evolution of the Peroxisome, 1969 (Box 41)
- Baggiolini, Christian de Duve, Masson and Heremans, Association of Lactogerrin with Specific Granules in Rabbit Heterophil, 1970 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, The Role of Lysosomes in Cellular Pathology, 1970 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Lysosome (Box 41)
- Peters, T. J., Subcellular Fractionation of the Enterocyte… (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Is There a Glycolytic Particle?, 1972 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Selection by Differential Molecular Survival- A Possible Mechanism of Early Chemical Evolution, 1987 (Box 41)
- Lazarow, et al, Biogenesis of Peroxisomes in Rat Liver and Candida tropicalis, 1987 (Box 41)
- Small, et al., Efficient Association of In Vitro Translation Products with Purified, Stable Candida tropicalis Peroxisomes, 1987 (Box 41)
- Rachubinski, Fujiki, and Lazarow, Isolation of cDNA Clones Coding for Peroxisomal Proteins of Candida tropicalis- Identification in Sequence of a Clone for Catalase (Box 41)
- In Memoriums, Fritz Lipmann, 1986 (Box 41)
- Alex Novikoff, Reminiscences, 1987 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Foreword to "Subcellular Pathology of Systemic Disease", 1987 (Box 41)
- de Duve, Christian, Foreword to "Lysosomes- Their Role in Protein Breakdown", 1987 (Box 41)
- Trager, Perkins, and Lanners, Malaria Vaccine, 1986 (Box 41)
- Declerck, Müller, Hydrogenosomal ATP-AMP Phosphotransferase of Trichomonas vaginalis, 1987 (Box 41)
- Müller, Hydrogenosomes of Trichomonad Flagellates, 1987 (Box 41)
- Lazarow, The Role of Peroxisomes in Mammalian Cellular Metabolism, 1987 (Box 41)
- Lazarow, Biogenesis of Peroxisomes-Implications for Zellweger Syndrome, 1987 (Box 41)
- Small and Lazarow, Import of the Carboxy-Terminal Portion of Acyl-Coa Oxidase into Peroxisomes of Candida tropicalis, 1987 (Box 41)